OLAYIWOLA ADEPOJU

Phone: +2347069768358

Email: layiwola008@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/olayiwola-adepoju

GitHub: https://github.com/layiwola008

SUMMARY

Over 5 years' experience in software and web application development; Proficiency in PHP, with experience in other languages (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js etc.); A self-driven young man who strives to exceed expectation and also make things happen individually and within a team.

SKILLS

Operating System: Windows

Programming Languages: PHP as the main Language for backend development **Front End Tools/Frameworks:** HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Vanilla JavaScript, React.js

Content Management System: WordPress, Joomla

Web Services Communication: JSON Databases: MySQL, PHPMyAdmin

Version Control: GitHub.

Command Line Interface: Gitbash **Agile Project Management Tool:** Trello

Design & IDE Tools: Visual Studio Code, Notepad++

Microsoft Office Tools: MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint

Graphics and Video Editing Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Wondershare Filmora

WORK EXPERIENCE

International Psychometrics Centre

Head of Info Tech. Department May 2021 – Till Date

- Built an online examination portal which resulted in over 1000% revenue increase
- Developed a Facebook-like social media platform to be advertised on CNN

Ilaji Sports Resort

Web Programmer 2020 – 2021

- Developed an online ticketing web app among others
- Developed a Full stack registration portal for Malaga CF (Spain), Nigeria football trial

Broadcasters International Magazine

Programmer

2020 - Till Date

- Built a Full Stack eLearning Solution for broadcasting courses
- Developed a WordPress Blog

PM Parrot Magazine

Webmaster and Lead Developer

2017 – Till Date

• Re-Developed and Manage WordPress Blog with 60% more readership

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATES

LinkedIn Learning

JavaScript Essential Training ---- (Feb. 04, 2022)

Pirple.com

DevOps: Intro To Server Administration ---- (Jan. 01, 2022)

Udemy

Complete Web Developer Course 2.0 ---- (2017)

Udemy

The Complete SEO Guide To Ranking Local Website ---- (2017)

Google

The Online Marketing Fundamentals ---- (2018)

Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-Ife

B. Sc., Sociology and Anthropology [Second Class Upper] ---- (2009 - 2013)

Government College Ibadan

SSCE --- (1998 - 2003)

GENERAL TRANSFERRABLE SKILLS

- Excellent writing and Editing; clear and concise
- Problem solving; thorough and tenacious.
- Management: time, projects and personnel
- Multitasking
- Effective communication of technical information to non-technical personnel

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Self-starting
- Proactive
- Multitasking
- Data Management Skills
- Open -minded
- Quick learning
- Adaptable

- Intelligent
- Ethical
- Team player
- Analytical

MISCELLANEOUS

Interests: Reading Tech Books, Travelling To New Places, Swimming, Playing Football, Learning Coding